We're ready for combat, I say I don't want that, what if I do?
Because cruelty wins in the movies
We've got a hundred thrown out speeches I almost said to you
Easy they come, easy they go
I jump from the train, I ride off the road
I never grew up, it's getting so old
Help me hold on to you
I've been the archer, been the prey
Who could ever lead me, darling?
Who could stay?
Dark side, a search for you dark side
But if I'm alright, I ain't here
I got out my nose just to spike my face
And I hate my reflection for years and years
I'm waking the night, I pace like a ghost
The room is on fire, invisible smoke
And all of my heroes die all alone
Help me hold on to you
I've been the archer, been the prey
So even who could ever lead me, darling?
Who could stay?
Because they see right through, they see right through
They see right through, can't you see right through me?
They see right through, they see right through me
I see right through me, I see right through me
All the king's horses, all the king's men
Could have put me together again
Cause all of my enemies started out friends
Help me hold on to you
I've been the archer, been the prey
Who could ever lead me, darling?
Who could stay?
Come back, ready for combat
Thanks for watching!